wingreenmarketing.com 2018-11-21

# Privacy Policy

What follows is WinGreen Marketing Systems’ (WinGreen) online privacy policy, which governs personal information gathered on our Internet site.

#### WinGreen’s Commitment to Online Security

Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. WinGreen encrypts billing information wherever WinGreen requests it. All WinGreen agents and contractors with access to personal information obtained on WinGreen Web sites are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their contract with WinGreen.

#### Personal Information that WinGreen May Collect Online

WinGreen collects personal information online, including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and facsimile numbers and billing information. WinGreen does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. In addition, no part of our sites is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 13.

#### How WinGreen Uses Personal Information Collected Online

Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails, handle your comments, and process billing and business requests related to program participation, and we will use such information to provide operational notices, in program record-keeping and to conduct research on industry marketplace practices. Our research may lead to the publication of aggregate demographical data but will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. At certain points where personal information is collected on our site, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about other WinGreen products and services. This election box only appears in places where the department collecting personal information maintains such lists. At any time you can add or remove your name from a WinGreen list by contacting us at [support@wingreenmarketing.com](mailto:%20support@wingreenmarketing.com).

#### How Your Information May Be Saved

In order to process your request, WinGreen may handle it itself, or refer the request to another appropriate organization for handling. By completing a request form or sending us a request or inquiry, you are allowing us to forward your information to the appropriate WinGreen organization, if necessary, and potentially also to one of WinGreen’s vendor partners. Consumer inquiries will be forwarded to the appropriate vendor partners by email, and consumers should recognize that this method of transmission may not be secure. Without submission of the requested information, WinGreen will not be able to process your request. WinGreen never sells or rents your personal or company information. WinGreen may release personal information under the following circumstances:

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;
  * Where our records indicate a company may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * To appropriate governmental authorities, where warranted by a company’s failure to participate in the advertising self-regulatory process or respond to an online privacy complaint, or where a company fails to honor the recommendations of the National Advertising Division, Children’s Advertising Review Unit or National Advertising Review Board;
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

#### Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please e-mail us with the new information or your review request at [support@wingreenmarketing.com](mailto:%20support@wingreenmarketing.com). Let us also know what led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.

#### Computer Tracking and Cookies

Our Web sites are not setup to track and collect personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used by our sales and marketing staff to provide better services to our clients, by offering additional information that may be of interest to them based on their inquiries on our web site. No personal information is collected.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. WinGreen uses identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use WinGreen sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data and do not read personal data from your machine.

#### Problems or Complaints with WinGreen’s Privacy Policy

If you have a complaint about WGMS compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [support@wingreenmarketing.com](mailto:%20support@wingreenmarketing.com).

#### CAN SPAM Act

WinGreen adheres to CAN SPAM through its adherence to the following requirements. For more details on the law click [CAN SPAM Act](http://www.business.ftc.gov/documents/bus61-can-spam-act-compliance-guide-business).

  1. Don’t use false or misleading header information. Your “From,” “To,” “Reply-To,” and routing information – including the originating domain name and email address – must be accurate and identify the person or business who initiated the message.
  2. Don’t use deceptive subject lines. The subject line must accurately reflect the content of the message.
  3. Identify the message as an ad. The law gives you a lot of leeway in how to do this, but you must disclose clearly and conspicuously that your message is an advertisement.
  4. Tell recipients where you’re located. Your message must include your valid physical postal address. This can be your current street address, a post office box you’ve registered with the U.S. Postal Service, or a private mailbox you’ve registered with a commercial mail receiving agency established under Postal Service regulations.
  5. Tell recipients how to opt out of receiving future email from you. Your message must include a clear and conspicuous explanation of how the recipient can opt out of getting email from you in the future. Craft the notice in a way that’s easy for an ordinary person to recognize, read, and understand. Creative use of type size, color, and location can improve clarity. Give a return email address or another easy Internet-based way to allow people to communicate their choice to you. You may create a menu to allow a recipient to opt out of certain types of messages, but you must include the option to stop all commercial messages from you. Make sure your spam filter doesn’t block these opt-out requests.
  6. Honor opt-out requests promptly. Any opt-out mechanism you offer must be able to process opt-out requests for at least 30 days after you send your message. You must honor a recipient’s opt-out request within 10 business days. You can’t charge a fee, require the recipient to give you any personally identifying information beyond an email address, or make the recipient take any step other than sending a reply email or visiting a single page on an Internet website as a condition for honoring an opt-out request. Once people have told you they don’t want to receive more messages from you, you can’t sell or transfer their email addresses, even in the form of a mailing list. The only exception is that you may transfer the addresses to a company you’ve hired to help you comply with the CAN-SPAM Act.
  7. Monitor what others are doing on your behalf. The law makes clear that even if you hire another company to handle your email marketing, you can’t contract away your legal responsibility to comply with the law. Both the company whose product is promoted in the message and the company that actually sends the message may be held legally responsible.
